Any gray scale image is interpreted by a computer as an array.
计算机会将任何灰阶图像解析为数组
A grid of values for each grid cell is called a pixel,
这是一个值网格 每个网格单元称为像素
and each pixel has a numerical value.
每个像素有一个数字值
Each image in the MNIST database is 28 pixels high and wide.
MNIST 数据库中的每个图像宽和高都是 28 个像素
And so, it's understood by a computer as a 28 by 28 array.
计算机将其看做 28 x 28 数组
In a typical gray scale image,
在典型的灰阶图像中
white pixels are encoded as the value 255,
白色像素用值 255 表示
and black pixels are encoded as zero.
黑色像素用 0 表示
Gray pixels fall somewhere in between,
中间值表示灰色像素
with light-gray being closer to 255.
浅灰更接近 255
We'll soon see that color images have
很快我们将发现 对于彩色图像
similar numerical representations for each pixel color.
每个像素颜色都有相似的数字表示法
These MNIST images have actually gone through a quick pre-processing step.
这些 MNIST 图像实际上已经过简单的预处理
They've been re-scaled so that each image has pixel values in a range from zero to one,
已经调整过范围 使每个图像的像素值都在 0 - 1 之间
as opposed to from 0-255.
而不是 0 - 255 之间
To go from a range of 0-255 to zero to one,
要从 0 - 255 变成 0 - 1
you just have to divide every pixel value by 255.
把每个像素值除以 255
This step is called normalization,
这个步骤叫做标准化
and it's common practice in many deep learning techniques.
在很多深度学习技巧中是很常见的做法
Normalization will help our algorithm to train better.
标准化能够提高算法的训练效果
The reason we typically want normalized pixel values
标准化像素值的原因是
is because neural networks rely on gradient calculations.
神经网络需要计算梯度
These networks are trying to learn how important or how
这些网络会尝试判断在确定图像类别时
weighty a certain pixel should be in determining the class of an image.
某个像素有多重要
Normalizing the pixel values helps these gradient calculations stay consistent,
标准化像素值有助于梯度计算保持一致
and not get so large that they slow down or prevent a network from training.
不会导致梯度太大 使训练速度下降或导致网络无法训练
So, now we have a normalized data,
标准化数据后
how might we approach the task of classifying these images?
如何分类这些图像呢？
Well, you already learned one method for classification,
你已经学过一种分类方法
using a multi-layer perceptron.
即使用多层感知器
How might we input this image data into an MLP?
如何将这个图像数据输入 MLP 中？
Recall that MLPs only take vectors as input.
MLP 仅接受向量作为输入
So, in order to use an MLP with images,
要对图像使用 MLP
we have to first convert any image array into a vector.
我们首先需要将图像数组转换为向量
This process is so common that it has a name, flattening.
这个流程很常见 有个专有名词 叫做扁平化
I'll illustrate this flattening conversion process on a small example here.
我将用一个小示例演示扁平化转换流程
In the case of a four-by-four image,
对于 4x4 图像
we have a matrix with 16 pixel values.
有一个包含 16 个像素值的矩阵
Instead of representing this as a four-by-four matrix,
我们可以将这个图像表示成有 16 个条目的向量
we can construct a vector with 16 entries,
而不是 4x4 矩阵
where the first first four entries of our vector
向量的前四个条目
correspond to the first wheel of our old array.
对应的是旧数组的第一行
The second four entries correspond to the second wheel and so on.
第二组四个条目对应第二行 以此类推
After converting our images into vectors,
将图像转换为向量后
they can then be fed into the input layer of an MLP.
就可以传入 MLP 的输入层
We'll see how this works and see how to produce
我们将在接下来的几个视频中学习背后的原理
a class prediction for any given image in the next few videos.
并学习如何针对任何给定图像生成类别预测结果